hi welcome back to the wheel of life
online which feet Iceland become a
leader online no pun and this is the
start of session seven in and Allah I
Walder is Jessica to chew and before I
forget I'll again like to thank Stanley
for translating ransom bloom lupus our
union but rima così cutter Stanley
cannot delete young man with him and him
and everything so to come at me
subculture somebody's India Kingdom
Allison so in session six we did a long
meditation I'm sorry with a little bit
too long Jessica table cook and elitist
young Punjab and in session seven again
we're gonna do another meditation this
meditation is called peacefully
reminding them of good and it doesn't
need its abutment and um I'm only Nutkin
break cotton Tonka Micah during and
after Salameh dance Apollo so we already
mentioned that as a person is dying
Radhika toasted over your would grant
babaco solar so those are very very good
if the atmosphere can be peaceful and
positive song and buy tickets awesome
anti-maidan positive
and just quietly talk to them don't Anja
Babic I didn't another break I remind
them after all the good things they've
done in this life looking up consumer
harm by Cabrera
Palala who Candela Peter Eenie
you know there is a famous Buddhist
ritual for helping a person in the Bardo
undertow and opens our booty some
tractor now on Tacloban to Oran Gilberto
and the name of the ritual is Changjo
dynamo para toda la junco choke means
yoga which means ritual chalk Marathi
chocolaty ritual Patera means
purification John bloody Permian and the
idea is that we attract the person the
needy and Allah katomina recorder into
to the prayers which are held during the
time they're in the bottle the audio I
am near the castle ah my dear brother
depart oh and monks and nuns who do the
prayers they might ask the family please
give us some piece of clothing that the
dead person was wearing a lot or maybe
their rosary or something they really
were attached to the unbearabie I want a
guarantee of lakukan - onto American
vertebrate or a cat or freaking Ibaka in
the Patera Marquitos sorta monkeytoes
Beatrice's ottoman urban america pakka
and then it's a very beautiful ritual
inured allopatric socket in de I did it
many times with my teacher for people
who passed away in the temple where we
lived dance I'm la coubre Cali Cali
demon guru Sai aunt Ora Ora Nieminen
garden here we heard about committing go
and this whole kind of complex ritual it
needs much of what are a little bit the
essence of the ritual in battle right
now is that we are attracting that
person to the room under Lockett amun-re
currently took a woman and by the way as
we'll explain later in this lumbering
book supporting kita card alaska monte
della Pugh coulomb Remini they can hear
you they can come but I can be someone
desire and America be sad that it
doesn't even matter what language you're
speaking in a perdu liebe shopping under
par chi they have the power to
understand become a milky Kamehameha and
then it's a very very touching ritual
because you remind them of all the good
that they did in their life in a
telepathic sonic minion to kuranda
monkey Nutkin break Asad Abu khattala
pedo
and we turn their mind to thinking about
some good seeds they made in their life
powerful good seeds Yong ki tamanna can
become an icon to poor people probably
bit by jeffrey calico Candela p2p focus
on quote even if there is my newest I
don't know angry their whole life or
fought with people their whole life la
concha car de Saussure again tomorrow
slowly the break cotton cardigan on so
more in America we already learned from
the learning text that if if they can
think about something good they did in
those crucial stages of the death
process he chose to the blood genetics
laboratory Capri cut up and put a bigger
contoso sorta like the wrinkle up and
department contained Ellen process
comedian it can drastically change the
direction of their future life ended up
a Sinatra's this Mubarak I do Pat Masada
Bunbury so we continue that
encouragement during the barter while
they're in the bottle while they're
between death and rebirth ticket
implanted come on breakn sama lamaa
peridot swapped American branded apart
Oh soft America under the entire kamati
and that coherent Kamali and those
beings were in the bar tonight spirit
life must look macro Canberra dedicate
open part to create a strange situation
they can see us
most often they can see their family
initiative on record about melihat
a toast wrinkled American definitely
have clogged America so let's say the
family is sitting in the kitchen the day
after the person died Jerrica patenella
to org america it up or so her East
Loudon determining go
and the family members are crying and
having breakfast you know dr. Gottman on
instance on a bun and then the part of
being many times they don't know they
dine mclubbe are those wrinkly but i
can't adapt oh my gosh so deafening god
and they're they're like why is everyone
crying but I can support II cannot
possible - and no one can hear them
did I do something on record so they
just keep eating you know did you make
up rush Makkah why don't I have
breakfast
I'm not passing up another set up an and
then finally they realized they died
come on
Akira my commentary my coming and they
can hear the family talking we can be
something artwork of each other it's
sometimes it's almost like there's a
piece of glass between them and the
family the girls poor dear despotic
etcetera break attacked orga
and there's sometimes they get
frustrated no one's listening to me they
bang on Paragon America first RC didn't
middle Kansai and and my kimono Kolkata
so in this meditation Jenny della
mediator see me first we're gonna get
choir for Tamaki talk imaginative now
and we're gonna go through those eight
technique meditations kind of faster you
talk and look at me because it'll be
chopped up then we're gonna choose a
family member or a friend communicate up
at mommy Liam gotta work at someone
maybe someone who's quite older someone
who's sick welcomes us or here to cook
to art of the Saarinen sake someone who
could conceivably die in the next few
months so Soren a monkey Matamata de la
república de pun
you
and of course we never know Oh suck it
up sometimes the healthiest person dies
first kind of appalling self Meninga
Lulu but let's just practice a be
marketable Lottie communicating with
this person in the in in the deathbed
and the Berto
well a kookn comedy Cassidy can order in
DD ranch on comity and then depart Oh
you
many kinds of meditation are just
practiced for real life when action is
meditation an aprotic on top in open
gotta
for example if you have a problem with
some other person you can you get angry
at them alone so against all touchy
kendama Maliki masala didn't or
enlightened and under string
breaker in your morning
meditations Alameda toss it back yonder
you can especially if you're gonna meet
them today you know you're gonna meet
them today marry me you can close your
eyes and practice meeting them today
under the Padma new top mother Lottie
Bert America Rainey and practice
remembering your diamond when you mean
done protecting a karma under Attica
birth of America
so in this meditation today the de la
méditerranée session 7 Shashi Kapoor
we're gonna go through this we can get
quiet quiet quiet with this aid
technique meditations and it does it
lapa technique and they were gonna go on
to imagining that someone we know is
dying and then has entered the bird
community talkin through smoke buy a
condo or so sorry Nikita can also look
at that community llama mosquito
we're gonna choose a real person we know
who might actually die in the field next
few months
keep track of mimesis or inherited a
tamil kanakam athena Lamott Republic
Bank
and we're gonna practice talking to them
about the good things they did get that
number lucky but beats our other than
what I gotta call her by Caracalla oka
and if the day of course the day will
come that people around you die someone
dies Casa del Conte besought to hurry
Oregon discrete random odd assortment
Inga and you will know what to do and
you will know how to help them under
control
I paid her Stella cook and another can
pouch our armament America and talking
to them encouraging them to remember the
good deed stayed in orbit journalism my
daughter breaking a bottle like a
Metallica and to activate those good
sense the note of my octave can be bit
bogus you can that's the essence of
junction it will indeed re Jojo so in a
way in that moment you become like those
monks or nuns who who are trying to help
the dead person the little kid Mannie
para started to under McGarry supported
the Arowana tobirama damage o muhammad
taraki
you are doing the exact same thing and
development a long summer process okay
so let's start
mari kita boleh
you
quiet we're done on cannabis I softly
closed Matata Tituba
long exhales push out the last air a
little bit extra push a moose on AAPIs
ba-da-da rock killer who got a truck
here domestic government extra and come
to listening to some sound in the room
where you are
tsubame döner kebab Rameshwar Adira at
the brotherbrother
10 berth here spool of apostasy
you
rest your mind on that sound like
resting your head on a pillow Lopakhin
pickin on Paris or I eat dosa party and
omelette acapella data's Banta
you
now let's go to a heartbeat for ten
breaths Skaro maraquita big architecture
dos llamas pullin up us
you
now let's go sit in the beautiful
meditation elegant meditation room
inside our heart scar America - dr.
Ahmed attended a luncheon - ketta
ten breaths as the world speed spell on
a path to leading my data
you
let's go to an inner chamber in her car
America Thomas Okawa Gallup chato
still sunny and nice fresh air inside my
sister Otaru terrazzo guarded Allah
you
the heart is beating now at a distance
October the toxic erotica Chauhan
you
try to get more and more quiet so
beloved Aquajet is market but now that's
the goal of this aim it or not to
generate lopunny me
you
now we touch the sugar crystal scar and
get a million - crystal Cola and we take
our mind inside Gotama so can't be
Connecticut alum still lots of light and
very fresh air
I see by doctor hired a new direction
got Sakura but tiny and anonymous and a
pika children are Danube Delta
you
now my mind is the whole Pacific Ocean
deep and right inside the sugar crystal
scrappy cannot saya de la salud Oh
Symmetra Pacific gallop de la parte de
la polla Christa
you
and now I include this guy to the ocean
currents I Abacha koopida real amid
kalau
silent and as promised to see and as
wide as the sky and it hires this guy
and his deep as the sea among that lost
puppy loud that sleep are long it does
think along it that's a golem loud
you
now I turn my mind off Scott on cyber my
dad could be Kira
block all the extra size extra ideas
block here some up Akira can eat any
extra
you
no I
under touch myself from my mind not my
mind do what he wants think what it
wants empty space and I'm not relating
to the mind I am gone
scarrans i am la busca de Ridder epic
era of their curriculum la coka not
acting in Kenya or piccola pointing it
at her Wakasa saya tidak Peru born in a
particular saya perky
you
now suddenly I'm in a hospital scram
Timothy Bisaya Daruma sake
I'm standing by the side of a bed so
your party lead is something toppity to
round up you can see a canal preparing
the departed or family member or friend
uncle target Ottoman maybe they're
elderly who can break us to that or
maybe they're sickly looking like a
socket socket done and there they are
dying in my imagination they are dying
but I cascara
imagine a society cascara and it's a
normal Hospital the need to room a
circuit normal lots of other noises
going on under bucks water line now very
probably there are other family members
or friends standing around starting a
Dakota kilometer Munir it is clearly I
don't have the chance to talk in a
perfect atmosphere to this person so I
did not put a button or a other
the lips wasa the supported in the door
Oh Amy
but this is what it's really like to to
be with the person who's dying a beanie
madam another sign number summary in
Saqqara
there will be many distractions a
Kannada might have come work there may
be strong emotions going on in the room
people crying
commander I'm OCD Dallas the machines
making noise nurses coming and going
machine wash water
Robert lalalala
let's practice this situation marketable
not teach it was a knee
it's not a perfect chance anymore
because I'm but the new sub portable but
it's almost always like that
happy hum Pierce Lala's potato and I'm
waiting for a good moment
that's I am a new goose are kept apart
without pushing this person or without
upsetting the other people in the room
and Pomodoro or on India powder bomb
Gangaram indeed Alum Rock
I'm going to direct the conversation so
I could Milan and Buttercup up to some
very positive things that this person
did during their life
grab a proper house are positively
lakukan or on you to slum hit the
breaker let's say it's my grandfather
history cut the cut line to caucus aya
young Sakura and we are practicing how
to help a person get Oscar gamble a
teacher I'm about to say Sora autopathy
and when the real time comes we will be
very used to it will be ready to pick
our walk to some another
t-bucket a contribution I can see up Oh
grandfather
Oh Kaka what was the thing you did as a
small child that made your mother most
happy hollandaise sauce toka chillin
mobile ebook appalling back here
and let them remember talk about it we
are converting each other cut their Oh
grandfather
caca when you were in your 20s
cut the camera did the Omer to Apple
hard for many people this is a an
idealistic time in their life lucky by
the quarter in the dalawa to ET le
stelle middle breaker
so what good things did you do
grandfather hold by capping so the
dealer cookin cupcake what did you do
that was helpful to other people over
and over a Bangkok Ella cooking broccoli
Kalyan to comment or online
you
and then the third party
in this moment in the hospital priority
task Atticus a teenager umezaki
can you can you remind them as some very
high-end beautiful karmic object Ibaka
and be summary not can break up a bra
bulge a karmic sauna ticket an actor can
you see okay Parker can be some red
Buddha Lisa come here para it's medicine
buried talking to you in II medicine
Buddha Buddha Obama Charaka Baraka so in
this very important moment in the moment
in stock up on develop you Breaka
mentioned some very holy day
Cebu kebab Republica tsuchi and then
best of all and comedian/actor bike
there is someone yeah
Oh Kaka what's the very best thing in
your life what is the thing you did
which we should remember you by APPA
halter bike Olympia Papa Holika Holika
nikita horoscope Kaka
what was the thing you did in your life
that helped the most people
Apollo Cocalico Candela p2p I'm about to
buy the hora
so and then other relatives will talk
and there will be interruptions from
nurses grab Atlantic on Barbie Chara
that a Kannada interpreter a parabrahma
but in a gentle and natural way the
pyramids are elaborate a lobby
bring the conversation back to one of
these four things
whopper talk about Kabbalah colosso
tutoring Bertolini
what's the first good thing you remember
doing for your mom Abajo por Tameka
kidnaps Adela coconut oh okay
what good things were you doing in your
youth in your 20s for example about how
by Kentucky lakukan the muscle just
walked over to a pool without any
Buddhist right now with his like Ibaka
we had Buddha up up with scara's
forget about Assad and was the very best
thing you ever did don't alter my camp
Rana Cocalico khazad-dûm
even if grandfather cannot answer if
they're if they're too sick to answer
okay delivery so much Oh up chickadee
ethanol Oh suck it up my job you can
still talk with them there must be
somebody surrender the deal and on some
level they will hear you want to be a
medical doctor now the last part of this
military scar on my contract remedy
tasini next day horribly couldna
in the afternoon Lee sorry hurry
grandfather passed away last night
okay money go to the malum
go to sit in a quiet place you look like
a tempeh tempeh like a bench at the park
is a very good place
spotty banco de tama Adela tompa g OCH
sonnet by and get quiet let me check it
on now maybe it can use some of the aid
quiet meditation commanded up a good not
constantly kept clapping many toss it up
now and then talk to grandfather and
comedian but beets are under that Kaka
it's a tradition to talk loud enough
that a person about two feet away about
about a meter away I could hear you sing
us a surah Naas guitar to a cocky junior
skater so to Mary Jo me some anger so
you're gonna talk out loud so I suggest
the park bench witches there's nobody
around and definitely chard is encrusted
this is our anthem anthem puting it up
and out of line and continue their
conversation with grandfather then Milan
should confirm the journey to the
bedrock
maybe he knows he died maybe he doesn't
even know kin D Italia Meninga KP Ibaka
the doctor he's behind the glass he
blocked a culture we are talking almost
one way through the glass grandfather
okay do you remember the conversation we
had yesterday my single stock up on kita
come on
did you remember anything more about the
best thing you did a pelagic encounter
by Camila Cabello keto the the dead
people in the Bardo or a matted apart oh
they really really appreciate someone
talking to them like they're still alive
my company Arvinder Makkar crisis our
own Beach eridan break us apart America
masahito
I have friends who have continued to
talk to their dead loved ones one one
woman whose daughter died when she was
about 20 so I am I'm gonna keep them at
the municipal beach I didn't order my
family touch entire ceremony 10 patria
mingle could be caduceus couple now she
has continued to go to the park every
day for for over ten years
you have to spoke ekodama step out Islam
Allah P that is pulled out and she still
talks to her daughter your mother Beach
other great Louis the daughter can hear
her
ten years or two she does spoonula
Domingo but it was a very great healing
for the mother total opinion once on a
payment in dunya and it created it made
that relationship forever beautiful the
need to Mambo to move in - llama
so you don't have to starve the under
the Affordable happy
these steps of the path in etapa Gary
Jalan the purpose is to become a Buddha
and a lot of Booga the path leads to
stepping to Buddhahood
Jolanda - Manu Joker kakugane
and there will come a day when I can be
besought - honey when I am a Buddha
because I am a traditional Buddha and
grandfathers Arthur Buddha that kakuka
Goethe we will meet again in the most
beautiful forms homologated calling it
and the two Buddhist will enjoy hanging
out together
Nabu got menikmati walked over summers
up so you will meet those people again
did he end up an but tomorrow or a
little laggy and it's not crazy to talk
with them and tell them indeed of
Keylong doable each other and even more
iconic mobile in America
so practice it daddy per second
let's take three deep exhales and offer
these good seats too of this good
meditation to other people who study
meditation moccasin Ichabod are online
as a golden life
stretching stretching across Maya city
well in the secod Messiah my country
regatta this world dunya in e world
little dunya
three Deepak cells Mogambo second column
golden rain Siam us could sit in
debuggers
you
slowly open your eyes mama come a time
take a good stretch for a guns to come
here we'll see if in the next session
some packet amudha simply cut now thanks
Danny
terima kasih sternly